<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollApp</string>
    <string name="textview">the age of space exploration. The Soviet Union was racing against the United States to seek advancements in their technology and be able to claim the victory title. The accomplishments attained by all participants marked the first steps in exploration, advancement in human scientific achievement, and a growth in the understanding of the universe. With each space exploration mission completed we make significant innovations and technological progressions that can be applied to many other areas other than just space. From the beginning of time humans have been compelled to explore newfound, unknown lands. The same incentives put a man on the moon as they did to bring men to explore new
    Is it safe to expand space exploration? In the US today there is debate about whether or not space exploration should be continued and further more into space. Though some people believe increasing it is not wise because it dangerous, the United States should increase space exploration because we can learn more, make better technology and gain a lot of money. Some people believe that manned missions of space explorations are far too dangerous and it’s too expensive. “Space contains the…moon in the night sky, but this iteration of human exploration poses unique problems. Past exploratory measures have taught us the consequences of overly zealous colonization:
        the genocide of millions of innocent people, the spread of hundreds of new infectious diseases, and the death of entire cultures. Therefore, entire programs and corporations work to weigh the costs and benefits of space exploration, determining how and why space exploration should take place. The most important factors to…Space exploration has been a goal among countries during the cold war. The two major powers of the time (1947-91), the United states and U.S.S.R competed among each other during a time, known as the Space race. However, as countries mobilized both technological and military power, they also joined the goal of space exploration. Several countries such as India, Japan and China, began to view space exploration as the next step to explore and to build wealth to their respective countries Space exploration is beyond our wildest dreams. Overcrowding stars, planets and mysteries in the open universe is unapparent and discovering everything that forms our world would be nearly impossible. To some people space exploration allows us to solve the wonders and understand a broader view of our universe we live in today. All matters in the universe, illuminating, were all merged together as one singularity - undergoing a rapid expansion to become a universe we stand on today. Space Exploration Why are people upset about NASA and their space exploration program? I am going to write about the reasons behind many people oppose space exploration and why many people encourage space exploration. This topic is of interest to me because as a people who wanted to explore space and believes that space exploration is important, it is an issue that needs to be addressed and needs to be funded again. This topic will be interesting to my readers because there</string>

</resources>